http://www.kodiakdailymirror.com/site/privacy.html

Store
We consider your privacy important. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent. Please read this Privacy Policy that you may understand how we use and protect your personal information.OverviewThis Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you and what may happen with that information.By accepting the Privacy Policy and the End user Terms of Service in the registration process, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the End user Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance of registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on November 01, 2008 for all users.1. Your Personal Information we collect.The primary purpose in collecting your personal information is to provide you with an effective, customized, and safe experience on our marketplace and forum network. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us or the specific business entity which you have registered with. Should you choose to use our services, you may be required to provide contact information, mailing information, billing information and other information as indicated on the on-line forms throughout the website. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional.We use your financial information, including credit card number, credit card billing address, expiration date, checking account name, address, bank routing number and bank account number to verify the accuracy of your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services.We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of our website(s) to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. “Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie”. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are “session cookies”, meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end on a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may mot be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently.You may also encounter “cookies” or other similar devices on certain pages that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.If you choose to post messages in our message area or leave feedback for other users, we will collect that information you provide us. We retain this information to provide customer support and empower users as they use the network.If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on this website(s), we may collect such information into a file specific for you.2. Our Use of Your Personal Information.We use the information you give to us to facilitate the services that you request. We use your personal information to: facilitate purchases on the website(s); troubleshoot account problems; collect the purchase of services and upgrade listing packages; inform you about online and offline offers, product, services, and updates; detect and protect against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our user terms and agreement; comply with any government regulation; facilitate use of discussion, chat or forum venues on the website(s); measure consumer interest in our products and services; and as otherwise described to you at the time of information collection. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.You agree that should you choose to purchase products and services on our website(s)You agree that we may use your personal information to benefit our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content, product and services offerings, and customize our website(s) with respect to content, layout and other services.You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you, in some cases targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the End user Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information.3. Our Disclosure of Your Personal Information.We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. The following describes some of the ways in which your personal information may be disclosed in the normal course of business as we provide our users with our services.Community Marketplace. After registration, every user has the ability to determine the extent to which they would like their personal information shared on the website. Users may choose to keep their entire personal information private (except mandatory-shared information such as user screen name, city, state, country, or share all of their personal information. Your mandatory-shared information is displayed on the website when you are logged in and is therefore available to the public. Your personal information that is optional to share is: first name, last name, address, postal code, phone number, and email address. You do not have to share your optional personal information on the website(s). Also, your user name and password are never displayed to the public. However, you have the ability to change your password if necessary. The “Edit My User Account” link of the user’s Account Preferences section is the place where changes to personal information can be made.Social Network. As with the Marketplace Network, every user has the ability to determine the extent to which they would like their personal information shared on the Social Network (such as blogs) of this website (s). The “Edit My User Account” link of the user’s Account Preferences section is the place where changes to personal information can be made. Should a user choose to send personal information, of any kind, whether it be information contained in the “personal information” section of the user account page or any other personal information that the user deems to share with other users of this website(s); user holds the owner of this website harmless and releases it from consequences of dissemination of personal information sent freely by user. This company has no control over personal information disseminated other than such personal information contained on the user’s “personal information” section of the users account page.Internal Service Providers. We may use third parties to help facilitate certain aspects of our business that we provide for you and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose or reason other than the specific service they are providing for us. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is regulated by their applicable privacy policy.Third Party Advertisers We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.orgLegal Requests. Due to subpoenas, court orders, government regulations and our rights to defend against legal claims, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Although we strive to protect your privacy, we cannot guarantee, nor should you expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.4. Knowledge and use of other users’ information.Because our service allows users to freely exchange information with one another, by entering into our End user Terms of Service Agreement, you agree, with respect to other users’ personal information that you obtain through this website(s), that the Company hereby grants to you the right to use such information only for: (a) Company related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose that a user expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use it for. Under no circumstances, except as defined in this section, can you disclose information about another user to any third party without the consent of that user. You agree that other users may use your personal information to communicate with you in accordance with this section. You agree to give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and review what information you may have collected about them.The Company will not tolerate spam. You are not authorized to add a user or users to your mailing list without their express consent.5. Control of your Password.You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password. We recommend that you do not disclose your User ID or password to any third parties. Should you share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account. We recommend that you review any third party Privacy Policies. If your password has been compromised, you should immediately change your password. If you lose control of your password you may lose control of your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf.6. Changing your Personal Information.We give you the ability to review and change the personal information you have submitted to us. This is done by logging into this website and entering your new information. Generally, we will not modify your personal information because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. We recommend that you promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate.Upon your request, we will deactivate your account, including contact information, billing information, and shipping information, from our active databases. To make this request, email our third party provider at support@radiatemedia.com. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible. However, we retain in our files some personal information you have requested to be removed to prevent fraud, assist with any investigations, enforce our policies and comply with any legal requirements as permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your request. However, such personal information will be deactivated from public and user viewing.7. Third Party ServicesThis Web site uses services provided by AP News Registry. AP News Registry collects content usage information and may use cookies in conjunction with this activity.Your continued readership of the Site means you accept the privacy policy of the AP News Registry. Please refer to the AP News Registry privacy policy at http://www.apnewsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx for further information.8. Security.Your personal information is stored on servers located in the United States of America. We use a variety of safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access, including encryption, “firewalls” and Secure Socket Layers. However, 100% totally secure and safe protection does not exist on the Internet.9. Notice of Policy Amendment.We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this website(s). All amended terms shall automatically be effective after they are initially posted.
9.2: Kodiak and the World's Second-Largest Earthquake~ $14.99 Free Shipping
Pre-Order 2021 Outhouse Calendar ~$9.99 Free Shipping
Support Local JournalismNow, more than ever, the world needs trustworthy reporting—but good journalism isn’t free.
Please support us by subscribing or making a contribution.
Subscribe or contribute
Latest e-Edition
Kodiak Daily Mirror
Kodiak Daily Mirror
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesReport: Kodiak nation’s 19th worst COVID hot spotSecond death related to COVID reported on the islandKodiak to move into "red" status on Monday as COVID cases increaseMan faces 32 hunting, fishing chargesIsland’s COVID cases continue to surge; Kodiak jumps to nation’s 15th hot spotObituary: Steven Paul NaultKIHA uses COVID money to pack freezersLocal man’s wilderness video reaches a million viewsRise in local cases could be linked to holiday gatheringsAlex Bill Shugak Sr. (11/16/1968 — 11/25/2020)
Images
Videos
CommentedBeloved bishop fondly remembered by his flock (1)Kodiak Alaska Video Final 3 (1)Republican Stutes sides with Alaska House coalition (1)Island’s COVID cases continue to surge; Kodiak jumps to nation’s 15th hot spot (1)Spotlight: Shane Parker (1)Spotlight: Marian Johnson (1)
Follow us on Facebook
kodiakdaily
Top Homes
80 ACRES - KIZHUYAK BAY
$260,000
Updated
13 hrs ago
ONION BAY! Just listed is a nice cabin with storage
$80,500
Updated
13 hrs ago
Alaska News
News Miner
North Pole legislator supports legal action contesting presidential election
Amanda Bohman,
abohman@newsminer.comUpdated
40 min ago
North Pole Rep. Mike Prax is among multiple Republican state legislators who sought for Alaska to join an unprecedented Texas lawsuit aimed at invalidating millions of votes in four other states and reversing the results of the presidential election.
News Miner
A virtual celebration of lights: Fairbanks Jewish community gathers online this year to celebrate Chanukah
Elisabeth Nadin
15 hrs ago
Almost 2,200 years ago, rebel warriors led by Judas Maccabeus defeated the Hellenic Greeks who had destroyed their temple and their way of life.
News Miner
Public is invited to pitch on where to build a new firing range
Alena Naiden,
anaiden@newsminer.com
15 hrs ago
“We’ll have an online zoom meeting so that the public can chat with us about the process,” said Steve Dutra, North Pole police department chief. “They can tell us whether they like it, they hate it, they’re neutral about it, they have concerns or questions.”
